Guide to the Nina Rosenblum Papers MSS.558
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VIII. Lock-Up: The Prisoners of Rikers Island and Beat Down: The Case of Raymond Alvarez, 1986-2000; 9 Linear Feet in 1 manuscript box, 6 record cartons, 2 cassette boxes, and 1 card box; 8 Betacam_SP; 2 Betacam; 25 audiocassette; 2 Digital_Betacam; 1 D-2; 1 MiniDV; 8.05 Gigabytes in 11 com
  - Subseries VIII.B. Beat Down, 1991-2000; 3.88 Linear Feet in 1 manuscript box, 1 record carton, 1 card box, and 1 cassette box; 24 audiocassette; 1 Betacam_SP; 1 D-2; 1 MiniDV
    - Alvarez, Raymond -- Correspondence, Drawings, Poems, and Civil Suit, 1991-1994 (Box 10, Folder 17-18)
    - Film Festivals, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Production Materials
      - Alvarez, Raymond
        - "The Best", circa 1991-1992 (Box 37, Audiocassette 558.0042)
        - Call from Rikers after 2nd Beating -- Raymond Speaks Second, July 15, 1991 (Box 37, Audiocassette 558.0132)
        - Call from Rikers after 2nd Beating and Tom Anferen, July 1991 (Box 37, Audiocassette 558.0041)
        - Conversation about Murder at Clinton, circa April 1991 (Box 37, Audiocassette 558.0149)
        - Nina Phone Call, circa June 1991 (Box 37, Audiocassette 558.0143)
        - Raymond, circa November 1991 (Box 37, Audiocassette 558.0128)
        - Raymond, September 8, 1992 (Box 37, Audiocassette 558.0142)
        - Raymond, October 7, 1992 (Box 37, Audiocassette 558.0138)
        - Raymond, October 29, 1992 (Box 37, Audiocassette 558.0130)
        - Raymond, January 4, 1993 (Box 37, Audiocassette 558.0127)
        - Raymond, undated (Box 37, Audiocassette 558.0133)
        - Raymond, undated (Box 37, Audiocassette 558.0137)
        - Raymond, undated (Box 37, Audiocassette 558.0040)
        - Talks about Beatings, September 28, 1992 (Box 37, Audiocassette 558.0134)
        - Telephone, July 13, 1991 (Box 37, Audiocassette 558.0140)
        - "They're Going to Hurt Me", August 1, 1991 (Box 37, Audiocassette 558.0136)
      - Beat Down: The Case of Raymond Alvarez -- Master, undated (Box 31, Betacam sp 558.0612)
      - Beat Down: The Case of Raymond Alvarez -- Master, January 26, 1995 (Box 32, D-2 558.0323)
      - Nancy -- Update, Jules, and Alvarez -- Letters, Phone Messages, and Newpaper Headlines, November 17, 2000 (Box 34, Minidv 558.0215)
      - Raymond and Tom Anferen, July 1991 (Box 37, Audiocassette 558.0139)
      - Raymond, Russell, Rocker, August 15, 1991 (Box 37, Audiocassette 558.0144)
      - Richard Wolf, Raymond Alvarez, and Carl Niles, July 1991 (Box 37, Audiocassette 558.0141)
      - Rikers "RPK", August 15, 1991 (Box 37, Audiocassette 558.0142)
      - Two Escape from Rikers, August 16, 1991 (Box 37, Audiocassette 558.0143)
      - Zivko and Karen
        - Interview -- 38 St and 9th Ave -- Tape 1, July 14, 1991 (Box 37, Audiocassette 558.0131)
        - T2 Master and Interview -- 38th St and 9th Ave, 1991-1992 (Box 37, Audiocassette 558.0129)
      - Zivko Pulisic, circa April 1991 (Box 37, Audiocassette 558.0148)
- Series IX. Slave Ship: The Testimony of the Henrietta Marie, 1994-1995; 0.88 Linear Feet in 2 manuscript boxes; 7.88 Megabytes in 8 documents
  This series consists of materials related to the documentary short, Slave Ship: The Testimony of the Henrietta Marie, which was commissioned in 1995 as part of the traveling exhibition, The Wreck of the Henrietta Marie. Materials related to the film, which is about the oldest slave ship wreck (1699) found off the coast of the United States, includes correspondence, some research materials, photographs and negatives, and marketing materials (in both analog and digital formats).
  - Budget, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Marketing Materials, 1994-1995
    - Electronic Records -- Photographs, FA_MSS_558_ER_31
    - Synopsis and Book Cover (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Photographs and Negatives, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Research Materials, circa 1994-1995; FA_MSS_558_ER_32
- Series X. A History of Women Photographers, 1995-2011; 3.69 Linear Feet in 1 manuscript box and 3 record cartons; 6 Betacam_SP; 10 VHS; 5.17 Gigabytes in 10 computer files
  This series relates to the 15 minute educational short, A History of Women Photographers, which was installed in 1996 in four institutions as part of the traveling exhibition with the same name. The exhibition, curated by Naomi Rosenblum and Barbara Tannenbaum, was based on Naomi Rosenblum's book, A History of Women Photographers. Materials related to the film include photographs from the book, shoot photographs, and film elements (such as the dramatic version, the documentary version, and a master copy for an Italian film festival).
  Arranged alphabetically by topic and alphanumerically within the last one.
  - Book Photographs, 2005-2010; FA_MSS_558_ER_47
  - Production Photographs, Slides by Simon Chaput, and Contact Sheet, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Production Videos
    - #1 Backyard, May 18, 1996 (Box 28, Betacam sp 558.0583)
    - #2 Astoria, May 18, 1996 (Box 28, Betacam sp 558.0584)
    - #4, May 20, 1996 (Box 28, Betacam sp 558.0581)
    - #5, May 18, 1996 (Box 28, Betacam sp 558.0610)
    - Akron Art Museum -- 5 of 8, undated (Box 32, Vhs 558.0322)
    - City Arts -- Women Photographers -- Episode 301, undated (Box 33, Vhs 558.0487)
    - Drama 1880s, May 18, 1996 (Box 28, Betacam sp 558.0608)
    - Dramatic Version, undated (Box 33, Vhs 558.0498)
    - Dramatization and Documentary -- 15 Minutes, undated (Box 33, Vhs 558.0496)
    - Electronic Recordings, 2004-2011; FA_MSS_558_ER_48
    - Final Dramatic Version, undated (Box 33, Vhs 558.0495)
    - Hillary 1920s, May 18, 1996 (Box 28, Betacam sp 558.0609)
    - A History of Women Photographers, 1996 (Box 32, Vhs 558.0329)
    - Italian Master Recording, undated; FA_MSS_558_ER_118
    - Ringl and Pit by Juan Mandelbaum, 1995 (Box 33, Vhs 558.0497)
    - Sunday Morning
      - "Women Photographers", February 2, 1997 (Box 38, Vhs 558.0182)
      - "Women Photographers" -- 3 of 8, February 2, 1997 (Box 32, Vhs 558.0321)
      - "Women Photographers" -- 4 of 8, February 2, 1997 (Box 32, Vhs 558.0320)
- Series XI. Walter Rosenblum: In Search of Pitt Street, 1979-2006; 11.27 Linear Feet in 4 manuscript boxes, 7 record cartons, 1 oversized custom box, 2 film cans, 1 small flat box, and 1 folder in a shared oversized box; 13 VHS; 2 16mm_film_reels; 32 Betacam_SP; 22 Digital_Betacam; 5 MiniDV; 2 U-matic; 10.56 Gigabytes in 70 computer files
  This series consists of materials related to Walter Rosenblum: In Search of Pitt Street, an hour-long documentary released in 1999 about the life and career of Rosenblum's father, the photographer Walter Rosenblum. Materials related to the production, marketing, and screening of the film, include scrapbooks, press, a script, photographs (print and digital), and film elements (such as interviews with Walter and Naomi Rosenblum, exterior shots, stills, and a subtitled version) on various media.
  - Subseries XI.A. Correspondence, 1999-2013; .44 Linear Feet in 1 manuscript box; 41.7 kilobytes in 2 computer files
    This subseries consists of letters, both analog and digital, regarding the making of this film.
    - Electronic Records, 2006-2013; FA_MSS_558_ER_49
    - Letters, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Subseries XI.B. Marketing Materials, 1999; .44 Linear Feet in 1 manuscript box; 48 kilobytes in 1 computer file
    This subseries contains materials related to the marketing of the film, such as a one-page description, press release, and postcard.
    - DVD Cover, circa 1999; FA_MSS_558_ER_50
    - Postcards, Press Release, and One-Pager, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Subseries XI.C. Press and Awards, 1993-2006; 2.21 Linear Feet in 2 manuscript boxes and 1 flat box
    This subseries includes publicity materials related to the film and awards received by the film and filmmakers. Materials consist of articles, reviews, award programs, and a publicity scrapbook.
    - Awards Correspondence and Programs, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Clippings, Articles, and Reviews, 1993-2006 (Box 12, Folder 6, Box Shared Fales 116, Folder 5)
    - Scrapbook, 1999-2001 (Box 12, Folder 7, Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Subseries XI.D. Production Materials, 1946-2006; 7.98 Linear Feet in 2 manuscript boxes, 6 record cartons, 1 small flat box, 1 oversized custom box, and 2 film cans; 13 VHS; 2 16mm_film_reels; 32 Betacam_SP; 22 Digital_Betacam; 5 MiniDV; 2 U-matic; 10.55 Gigabytes in 65 computer files
    This subseries consists of materials related to the production of the film, such as transcripts, photographs, a proposal, video recordings, notebooks, and music cue sheets.
    - Astoria -- Video Recordings
      - Master, May 18, 1996 (Box 26, Betacam sp 558.0883)
      - Tape 3, May 18, 1996 (Box 26, Betacam sp 558.0895)
      - Tape 4, May 18, 1996 (Box 26, Betacam sp 558.0893)
      - Tape 5, May 18, 1996 (Box 27, Betacam sp 558.0172)
      - Tape 7, May 18, 1996 (Box 27, Betacam sp 558.0123)
      - Tape 9, May 18, 1996 (Box 27, Betacam sp 558.0124)
    - Audio Transcripts, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 10-12)
    - California -- Video Recordings
      - Judy Keller -- Master -- Tape 2, April 27, 1998 (Box 26, Digital betacam 558.0886)
      - Master -- Tape 1, April 27, 1998 (Box 26, Digital betacam 558.0897)
      - Master -- Tape 3, April 27, 1998 (Box 26, Digital betacam 558.0887)
    - Cinema at Pitt Street -- Enlarged Photograph by Walter Rosenblum, 1938 (Box 63)
    - Exteriors -- Video Recordings
      - Rivington and Pitt Streets -- Tape 4 -- Master, April 5, 1996 (Box 30, Betacam sp 558.0533)
      - Tape 1 -- Master, April 5, 1996 (Box 30, Betacam sp 558.0535)
      - Tape 2 -- Master, April 5, 1996 (Box 30, Betacam sp 558.0534)
      - Tape 3 -- Master, April 5, 1996 (Box 30, Betacam sp 558.0532)
    - Interviews and Stills -- Video Recordings
      - Her Study -- Tape 7 -- Interview Master, April 24, 1998 (Box 26, Digital betacam 558.0894)
      - Interviews and 2 Stills #9, April 24, 1998 (Box 26, Digital betacam 558.0900)
      - Stills -- Darkroom -- South Bronx, April 22, 1998 (Box 26, Digital betacam 558.0901)
      - Stills -- Darkroom -- South Bronx, April 22, 1998 (Box 39, Minidv 558.0071)
      - Stills -- East Harlem, April 22, 1998 (Box 26, Digital betacam 558.0899)
      - Stills -- East Harlem, April 22, 1998 (Box 27, Digital betacam 558.0121)
      - Stills -- Haiti #5, April 24, 1998 (Box 26, Digital betacam 558.0902)
      - Stills and Interview #8, February 24, 1998 (Box 30, Digital betacam 558.0531)
      - Stills -- Master, April 22, 1998 (Box 26, Digital betacam 558.0884)
      - Stills -- Master -- #6, undated (Box 26, Digital betacam 558.0891)
      - Stills -- Photo League and Andre, May 4, 2001 (Box 26, Betacam sp 558.0890)
    - Master Recordings and Completed Film
      - Master, September 28, 1995 (Box 26, Betacam sp 558.0875)
      - Master -- Reel 2, September 28, 1995 (Box 33, Betacam sp 558.0043)
      - Master -- Reel 3, September 28, 1995 (Box 33, Betacam sp 558.0044)
      - Master -- Channel 1, undated (Box 28, Vhs 558.0599)
      - Subtitled, undated (Box 30, Betacam sp 558.0540)
      - Walter Rosenblum: In Search of Pitt Street, February 8, 1996 (Box 30, U-matic 558.0538)
      - Walter Rosenblum: In Search of Pitt Street -- Print, 1999; cuid41402 (Box 51, 16mm film reels 558.0287)
      - Walter Rosenblum: In Search of Pitt Street -- Print, undated; cuid41403 (Box 52, 16mm film reels 558.0288)
      - Walter Rosenblum: In Search of Pitt Street, undated (Box 39, Minidv 558.0073)
    - Music Cue Sheets, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Negatives, circa 1998-1999 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Norfolk -- Video Recordings
      - Dining Room Table and Study -- Reel 5, September 1, 1995 (Box 27, Betacam sp 558.0173)
      - Lisa Tennis -- Film Transfer Master -- Reel 8, September 1, 1995 (Box 27, Betacam sp 558.0122)
      - Master, April 14, 1997 (Box 26, Betacam sp 558.0882)
      - Mom Backyard -- Film Transfer Master -- Reel 7, September 1, 1995 (Box 27, Betacam sp 558.0118)
      - Norfolk, June 18, 1997 (Box 28, Vhs 558.0598)
      - Protection Master, June 18, 1997 (Box 28, Betacam sp 558.0605)
      - Tennis -- Reel 2, September 1, 1995 (Box 27, Betacam sp 558.0120)
      - Tennis and Naomi Garden -- Master, September 1, 1995 (Box 26, Betacam sp 558.0889)
      - Walter and Family/Tennis, 1997 (Box 28, Vhs 558.0595)
      - Walter in Front of Computer, September 1, 1995 (Box 28, Betacam sp 558.0602)
    - Notebooks and Daily Planner, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Photographs, 1946-2006; FA_MSS_558_ER_51
    - Photographs and Contact Sheet, circa 1998-1999 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Proposal, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Shoot 1 -- Video Recordings
      - 101, April 5, 1996 (Box 39, Minidv 558.0528)
      - 102, April 5, 1996 (Box 39, Minidv 558.0529)
      - 102, April 5, 1996 (Box 38, Vhs 558.0187)
      - 104, April 5, 1996 (Box 39, Minidv 558.0530)
    - Slides, circa 1998-1999 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Video Recordings
      - #10, April 26, 1998 (Box 26, Digital betacam 558.0898)
      - #11, April 26, 1998 (Box 26, Digital betacam 558.0896)
      - 106M Pitt Street, February 19, 1979 (Box 27, U-matic 558.0177)
      - Greenberg Gallery, June 11, 1997 (Box 28, Vhs 558.0585)
      - Metropolitan Museum -- Master, undated (Box 26, Digital betacam 558.0888)
      - Reels 1-4, September 28, 1995 (Box 28, Vhs 558.0588)
      - "Talkin' Pictures", October 7, 1999 (Box 28, Vhs 558.0594)
    - Walter -- Video Recordings
      - D-Day, August 5, 1995 (Box 28, Vhs 558.0592)
      - First Apartment and Darkroom, 1996-1998; FA_MSS_558_ER_123
      - Interview, July 26, 2000 (Box 28, Vhs 558.0591)
      - RIT -- Dub, February 6, 1991 (Box 28, Vhs 558.0593)
      - Shoot 1 -- Tape 1, April 5, 1996 (Box 31, Betacam sp 558.0617)
      - Shoot 1 -- Tape 2, April 5, 1996 (Box 31, Betacam sp 558.0613)
      - Shoot 1 -- Tape 3, April 5, 1996 (Box 31, Betacam sp 558.0614)
      - Shoot 1 -- Tape 4, April 5, 1996 (Box 26, Betacam sp 558.0892)
  - Subseries XI.E. Screenings and Festivals, 1999-2006; .44 Linear Feet in 1 manuscript box; 2.8 Megabytes in 2 computer files
    This subseries includes materials related to the scrrening of the film and participation in film festivals; materials include festival programs, schedules, and correspondence.
    - Correspondence, Schedules, and Programs, 1999-2006 (Box 12, Folder 3-5)
    - Photographs, circa 1999; FA_MSS_558_ER_52
- Series XII. Sly and Jimi: The Skin I'm In, 2000-2010; 4.77 Linear Feet in 3 manuscript boxes, 3 record cartons, and 1 shared LP box; 1 Super_8mm_Film_Reel; 3 Betacam_SP; 10 VHS; 9.79 Gigabytes in 13 computer files
  This series focuses on materials related to Sly and Jimi: The Skin I'm In, a feature documentary released in 2000 that highlights the music of Jimi Hendrix and Sly and the Family Stone. Materials related to the production, marketing, and screening of the film consist of a proposal, production book, and film elements (such as rough cuts, interviews, and master recordings) on various media.
  Arranged alphabetically into three subseries and alphanumerically within each one.
  - Subseries XII.A. Correspondence, 2000-2010; .44 Linear Feet in 1 manuscript box; 50.8 kilobytes in 3 computer files
    This subseries contains letters, both analog and digital, and a proposal related to the making of the film.
    - Emails, circa 2000; FA_MSS_558_ER_53
    - Letters, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Multi-Platform Proposal, 2010; FA_MSS_558_ER_56
  - Subseries XII.B. Marketing Materials, 2000; .44 Linear Feet in 1 manuscript box; 56 kilobytes in 1 computer file
    This subseries includes materials related to the marketing of the film, including an advertisement and announcement.
    - Advertisement, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - DVD Cover, circa 2000; FA_MSS_558_ER_54
  - Subseries XII.C. Production Materials, 2000-2010; 4.13 Linear Feet in 1 manuscript box, 3 record cartons, and 1 shared LP box; 1 Super_8mm_Film_Reel; 3 Betacam_SP; 10 VHS; 9.79 Gigabytes in 9 computer files
    This series contains materials related to the production of the film, such as video recordings of interviews and rough cuts, a script outline, photographs, and a production book.
    - Electronic Recordings and Photographs, 2004-2010; FA_MSS_558_ER_55
    - Film Master, August 1, 2000 (Box Shared Fales 104, Super 8mm film reel 558.0020)
    - Interviews
      - David Kapralik -- Sly Stone's Manager, circa 2000 (Box 33, Vhs 558.0492)
      - Jerry Brandt, August 22, 2000 (Box 33, Vhs 558.0490)
      - Rose Stone at Home -- Reseda, California, July 20, 2000 (Box 32, Betacam sp 558.0453)
      - Rose Stone at Home -- Reseda, California, July 20, 2000 (Box 32, Vhs 558.0335)
    - Photographs, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Production Book, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Rough Cuts -- Video Recordings
      - Rough Cut, circa 2000 (Box 30, Betacam sp 558.0543)
      - Rough Cut, September 2, 2000 (Box 33, Vhs 558.0488)
      - Rough Cut, September 2, 2000 (Box 33, Vhs 558.0489)
      - Version 1, circa 2000 (Box 33, Vhs 558.0486)
    - Script Outline, Clearances, and Credits, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Super 8 Transfer, circa 2000 (Box 30, Betacam sp 558.0542)
    - Treatment -- Draft, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Series XIII. Unintended Consequences, 1998-2008; 11.69 Linear Feet in 1 manuscript box, 5 record cartons, 2 small flat boxes, 5 cassette boxes, and 1 folder in a shared oversized box; 4 DAT; 9 Betacam_SP; 2 Hi8; 190 MiniDV; 1 VHS-C; 2 audiocassette; 2.71 Gigabytes in 22 computer files
  This series contains materials related to Unintended Consequences, a documentary short produced in association with the Drug Policy Institute in 2001. The film focuses on the impact of the Rockefeller Mandatory Minimum Drug Laws on families and communities in New York City. It follows a group called The Mothers of the New York Disappeared and Terrence Stevens, a former incarcerated individual who served nine years of a 15-to-life sentence before being granted clemency. Materials related to the production, marketing, and screening of the documentary consist of press, contracts, a scrapbook, film elements (such as interviews; specific scenes; and eight-, nine-, and 15-minute versions) on various media, and research materials (including videos on the Rockefeller Drug Program). Also included in the series are materials related to In Arms Reach, a community organization founded in 2002 by Terrence Stevens to support economically challenged youth, especially those impacted by incarceration. Materials include various video and audio recordings by Rosenblum (who also served as a teacher and informal advisor to the program), informational material (such as brochures) about the organization, and photographs.
  - Subseries XIII.A. In Arm's Reach, 2001-2008; 3.35 Linear Feet in 1 manuscript box, 2 small flat boxes, and 3 cassette boxes; 49 MiniDV; 2 audiocassette; 21.1 Megabytes in 15 computer files
    This subseries includes materials related to In Arm's Reach, a community organization founded by Terrence Stevens, one of the subjects of the film. Materials include audio and video recordings of the youth involved in the program, photographs, and an informational brochure.
    - Audio Recordings
      - Terrence on Fancy Broccoli -- IAR 054, 2001 (Box 62, Audiocassette 558.0229)
      - Unintended Consequences -- IAR 055, 2001 (Box 62, Audiocassette 558.0232)
    - Brochure, Photographs, and Press, 2001-2007 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Video Recordings
      - Chris Lee and T -- Recruitment in the City, April 20, 2002 (Box 35, Minidv 558.0717)
      - Event Photographs and Video Log, 2003-2008; FA_MSS_558_ER_57
      - Graduation Tripod -- 1 of 2, April 20, 2001 (Box 39, Minidv 558.0192)
      - Graduation Tripod -- 2 of 2, 2001 (Box 40, Minidv 558.0351)
      - IAR 002, May 10, 2002 (Box 40, Minidv 558.0359)
      - IAR 003 -- EG Logic Mod, August 2, 2002 (Box 40, Minidv 558.0360)
      - IAR 004, August 23, 2002 (Box 40, Minidv 558.0361)
      - IAR 005 -- T to Bank -- First Day, August 23, 2002 (Box 40, Minidv 558.0362)
      - IAR 006 -- Day 1 City Call, August 24, 2002 (Box 40, Minidv 558.0363)
      - IAR 007, September 8, 2002 (Box 40, Minidv 558.0364)
      - IAR 008, September 8, 2002 (Box 40, Minidv 558.0365)
      - IAR 009, September 8, 2002 (Box 40, Minidv 558.0366)
      - IAR 010 --Class 2, September 14, 2002 (Box 40, Minidv 558.0367)
      - IAR 011 -- Class 2, September 14, 2002 (Box 40, Minidv 558.0368)
      - IAR 012 -- Class 2, September 14, 2002 (Box 40, Minidv 558.0369)
      - IAR 013, September 21, 2002 (Box 40, Minidv 558.0370)
      - IAR 018 -- Sony, September 28, 2002 (Box 40, Minidv 558.0371)
      - IAR 019 -- Joshua Clan Visual, October 4, 2002 (Box 40, Minidv 558.0350)
      - IAR 021 -- Alex and J.J. Meeting/Alex Talking about J.J., October 4, 2002 (Box 40, Minidv 558.0245)
      - IAR 022, October 5, 2002 (Box 40, Minidv 558.0347)
      - IAR 023, October 5, 2002 (Box 40, Minidv 558.0348)
      - IAR 024 -- T's Birthday and Judge, October 7, 2002 (Box 40, Minidv 558.0349)
      - IAR 025 -- School Kimberly, October 11, 2002 (Box 40, Minidv 558.0343)
      - IAR 026 -- Kimberly H.S. Fair, October 19, 2002 (Box 40, Minidv 558.0344)
      - IAR 027 -- Kimberly H.S. Fair, October 19, 2002 (Box 40, Minidv 558.0345)
      - IAR 028 -- Neighborhood Shooting and Talking to the People That Knew Daniel, October 24, 2002 (Box 40, Minidv 558.0346)
      - IAR 029 -- Lil Rob Grandfather in Shelter, November 1, 2002 (Box 40, Minidv 558.0243)
      - IAR 030, November 2, 2002 (Box 40, Minidv 558.0242)
      - IAR 031 -- Christopher, November 2, 2002 (Box 40, Minidv 558.0241)
      - IAR 032 -- Open House, November 7, 2002 (Box 40, Minidv 558.0244)
      - IAR 033 -- Kim Open House, November 7, 2002 (Box 40, Minidv 558.0246)
      - IAR 034 -- The Whitney Teen Night, November 8, 2002 (Box 40, Minidv 558.0247)
      - IAR 035 -- Janeatte WT, November 8, 2002 (Box 40, Minidv 558.0248)
      - IAR 036 -- Whitney, November 9, 2002 (Box 40, Minidv 558.0249)
      - IAR 037 -- Filming the Student Tutoring, November 12, 2002 (Box 40, Minidv 558.0250)
      - IAR 038, November 14, 2002 (Box 40, Minidv 558.0251)
      - IAR 040 -- Greenhaven Visit, November 23, 2002 (Box 40, Minidv 558.0252)
      - IAR 042 -- NYU Public Library Visit -- Dub, undated (Box 40, Minidv 558.0337)
      - IAR 043 -- Whitney MVS Poetry, Fall 2002 (Box 40, Minidv 558.0338)
      - IAR 044 -- NYC Public Library Visit, Fall 2002 (Box 40, Minidv 558.0352)
      - IAR 045 -- Prison Car, November 1, 2002 (Box 40, Minidv 558.0339)
      - IAR 046 -- NR Exc Tutoring, Fall 2002 (Box 40, Minidv 558.0340)
      - IAR 047, undated (Box 44, Minidv 558.0715)
      - IAR 048 -- Mrs. Best, undated (Box 40, Minidv 558.0353)
      - IAR 049 -- Press Conference -- Tape Quenelle, September 16, 2003 (Box 40, Minidv 558.0354)
      - IAR 050 -- Demo, October 4, 2003 (Box 40, Minidv 558.0355)
      - IAR 051 -- Vera 2, November 15, 2003 (Box 40, Minidv 558.0356)
      - IAR 052 -- Vera, November 15, 2003 (Box 40, Minidv 558.0357)
      - IAR 053, undated (Box 40, Minidv 558.0240)
      - IAR 056, undated (Box 40, Minidv 558.0358)
  - Subseries XIII.B. Marketing Materials, Honors, and Press, 2001-2002; .44 Linear Feet in 1 manuscript box; 43 kilobytes in 1 computer file
    This subseries includes materials related to the marketing of the film, awards received by the film, and publicity about the film. These materials include award correspondence, a VHS cover, press releases, and reviews.
    - Award, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - DVD Cover, circa 2001-2002; FA_MSS_558_ER_58
    - Reviews and Articles, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Screenings, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Stickers, Labels, and Photographs, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 11)